<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_title">Friendly Player</string>
    <string name="folders_descriprion">
        This activity contains all folders that include music files.
        Folders sorted by name. To accomplish that we cna use "Media Store". I found this solution on
        Stuck OverFlow https://stackoverflow.com/questions/11285288/android-mediastore-get-distinct-folders-of-music-files
    </string>
    <string name="all_music_descriprion">
        This activity should display all music files stored in current
        divice sorted by name. Other functionality can be attached to this activity, such as: play randomly.
        play one-by-one ... For example i can learn how to do that from this article
        http://www.androiddevelopersolutions.com/2015/12/android-media-store-tutorial-list-all.html
    </string>
    <string name="music_store_description">
        I found "Android Pay API" in the internet: https://developers.google.com/android-pay/tutorial.
        There is full description of how it can be used. So, I think with a right amount of time I can
        get it. There is a tutorial of how to implement this API and examples of how it can be used.
        In my case it can be like user go to the music store, choose album or song, pay for this song,
        and get temporary link to download this song.
    </string>
    <string name="meditation_spacebase_description">
        This activity is my idea. This activity can contain links for meditation music or video files from internet.
        Can be sorted by amount of likes from users for example. This is something that can make this player different
        from other music players.
    </string>

    <string name="now_playing_description">
        This activity will show currently playing music file. Will show a picture of an album, Album name,
        song title, artist. This information can be taken using MediaStore. And here is a link to solution that
        I found in the internet: https://stackoverflow.com/questions/33360055/android-how-to-get-audio-detail-from-audio-file  .
    </string>
    <string name="folders">Folders</string>
    <string name="all_music">All music</string>
    <string name="now_playing">Now playing</string>
    <string name="music_store">Music store</string>
    <string name="meditation_spacebase">Meditation SpaceBase</string>
</resources>
